## Denis Nagornyi

SENIOR PYTHON ENGINEER | PYTHON/DJANGO DEVELOPER | TBILISI, GEORGIA (GMT+4)



**8+ YEARS OF EXPERTISE** 

+995 511 228 446 Linkedin denis.nagornyi0@gmail.com

#### **Profile**

Python developer with 8 years of experience in teams of all sizes, from startups to enterprises. Equally effective as a team player or a "one-person orchestra," handling everything from requirements to DevOps.

Known for delivering solutions that address 80% of business needs with 20% of the effort.

### Experience

#### SENIOR PYTHON DEVELOPER AT EMERGING TRAVEL GROUP. NOVEMBER 2023 - NOW;

Developed a property management system (PMS) tailored for short-term rental hosts.

- Designed and implemented a custom matching algorithm, tripling the number of listed properties (+50,000 apartments) on the platform, driving significant revenue growth.
- Enabled the onboarding of 20,000 additional properties in key high-demand regions through a streamlined, data-driven approach, with potential for even greater results upon full-scale ETL implementation.
- Simplified and accelerated property activation by addressing key host pain points, significantly increasing platform availability and competitiveness in critical markets.

This solution not only enhanced supply acquisition but also positioned the company ahead of competitors with minimal investment of time and resources.

# SENIOR BACKEND ENGINEER I AT SUPER DISPATCH INC., KANSAS (REMOTE) FEBRUARY 2022 – NOVEMBER 2023; 1 YR 10 MOS

Development and support of public, web backend and mobile applications APIs

- Set up responsive search p99 delay 3s by optimizing documents in Elasticsearch
- Achieved 99.87% availability and reduced time to fix bugs from 2 weeks to several hours by integrating Datadog monitoring

**SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER AT TETRIKA SCHOOL, MOSCOW. JANUARY 2021 – FEBRUARY 2022; 1 YR 2 MOS** Involved in core processing and marketing tasks.

- Refactored legacy code that integrates CPA and payment processing, so integrating new ad network or payment system takes 3-5 days instead of month.
- Implemented custom per-block caching for dynamic landings for lowering load times and cpu cost.

MIDDLE PYTHON DEVELOPER AT DRIMTIM.IO, MOSCOW. MARCH 2018 - JANUARY 2021; 2 YRS 11 MOS

PYTHON ENGINEER; HONEYTEDDY. SEPTEMBER 2016 - MARCH 2018. 1 YR 7 MOS

#### Education

MEng, Computer Science and Informatics, Moscow Aviation Institute (National Research University), Moscow 2021.